thomex.com 2014-03-31

# Privacy Policy - World Industrial Reporter : World Industrial Reporter

So that you can better protect your privacy, Thomas Publishing Company, LLC (“Thomas” or “we” or “us”) provides this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your personal information is collected and used. If you do not agree with the practices explained in this policy, do not complete the registration form when signing-up for WorldIndustrialReporter.com or contact us at info@worldindustrialreporter.com to request that your registration be cancelled.

**PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Thomas will never ask you to provide us with personally identifiable information such as your name, e-mail address, physical address or phone number in order to access the site.

If you choose to post a comment to the site, you will be asked to provide a name and e-mail address. This information will be stored, but will not be used for any purpose other than to allow you to post your comment and so that we may contact you regarding that post in keeping with our copyright policy.

If you choose to subscribe to the World Industrial Reporter newsletter via the site, we will only ask for your e-mail address, company name, major job function, and primary area of concern (from a pre-populated list of choices). We will use this information to send you the requested newsletter and to tailor the contents of the newsletter to your area of interest.

We never share any personally identifiable information with any third parties, except as set forth below in the E-mail Communications Policy section of this policy.

During your visit, we may collect certain non-personally identifiable information, as detailed below, regarding your visit to the website. We will use this information to help customize and improve your site experience and/or to provide aggregated information to our advertisers and partners.

**COMMUNICATING WITH SUPPLIERS**

If you use the provided link to generate an e-mail to a listed company, you will be directly communicating with a third party. Thomas will not be privy to or store any information you share, but you will, of course, be sharing information with the recipient of the e-mail. Thomas is not responsible for and has no control over the privacy policies of any such e-mail recipients.

**E-MAIL COMMUNICATIONS POLICY**

By signing up with Thomas to receive the World Industrial Reporter Newsletter, and providing us with your e-mail address you agree to accept essential communication concerning the newsletter and its delivery. By signing up to receive the newsletter, you are also agreeing that we may send you e-mails from our trusted partners and other third parties containing information and offers that you may find of interest.

All non-essential communications from Thomas or one of our trusted partners will contain a link or instructions for opting out of future such communications. If the message you receive has been sent on behalf of one of our partners, the message will contain two separate means of opting out. One opt out will be from the Thomas e-mail list and the other opt out will be to remove you from the partner’s e-mail list. Please Note: to comply with the United States CAN-SPAM act, opting out from future communications from a Thomas partner will require your e-mail address be given to that partner so that they may add it to their own do not mail list.

**COOKIES & LOGGING**

A cookie is a piece of text that a web server can store on your computer’s hard disk. Cookies allow a website to store information on your computer and later retrieve it. Usage of a cookie is not linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Thomas uses cookies to: automate log in, permit guest access, enable personalization, measure site usage, and record user preferences. Thomas also uses java script tags for the purpose of site analytics.

Thomas also makes extensive use of web logging to understand the usage of our services, diagnose problems and identify future enhancements to our site. In addition to logging the pages viewed, and features used, our logs, cookies and tags may collect referring IP addresses, domain names, browser type and language, the date and time of visit, as well as information about your ISP, referring URL, or the search term that led to the site, and, where available, information on the sector of business of the originating IP address.

Cookies, java script tags and logging are used in the reporting and analysis of our website some of which will be shared with Thomas vendors and advertisers. This information is never tied to personally identifiable information. We also may use the non-personal information we gather to personalize the site for you and provide information relevant to a particular industry.

**REPORTING**

Thomas is able to offer WorldIndustrialReporter.com for free on the Internet as a direct result of the paid support of the manufacturers who advertise on our site. As a result we provide these advertisers with reports of non-specific information on the usage of WorldIndustrialReporter.com. This reporting can be based on any of the information collected by WorldIndustrialReporter.com and can include demographic information (Industry, Company Size, Job Function, Job Title and City) and your company name. Again, as stated in the Information section of this notice, your personal information is never divulged.

**DATA SECURITY**

Thomas uses reasonable precautions to keep user information disclosed to us secure. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place reasonable physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect. However, we cannot ensure or warrant that any information you transmit to us will stay safe and secure and you do so at your own risk

**CHANGES TO THIS POLICY**

Thomas reserves the right to change this policy as required. Users should review this policy periodically or prior to any use of this site as continued use of the site following any change of the policy will constitute your acknowledgement and acceptance of the policy.

**CONTACTING THOMAS**

If you have any questions regarding this policy please contact us via e-mail at info@WorldIndustrialReporter.com or by mail at:

Thomas Publishing Company, LLC  
5 Penn Plaza  
New York, NY 10001

Rating: 0.0/ **10** (0 votes cast)
